

ACHMAD FACHRUL

Objective

I am a lifelong learner and highly open to new experiences. I recently graduated from the Department of Informatics and Computer Engineering, Makassar State University. I prefer to work multi-talented, either on the field or on the front line. I also have proficient skills in processing administrative data using Microsoft Excel.

Education

Makassar State of University

Bachelor's Degree Informatics and Computer Engineering

Work Experience

PT. Telkom Indonesia (Internship)

Indihome technical support

 working on indihome network installation projects with more than 100 customers in 3 months and doing network maintenance with a team of technicians

Frontend Web Development (Freelancer)

- Developing web portfolios
- Developing landing page
- Developing company profile

Graphic Design (Freelancer)

- Creating a logo design
- Creating poster design
- Brochure design
- Making business cards

Organization

Himpunan Pengusaha Muda Indonesia PT UNM

creative economy and telecommunications department staff

Himpunan Mahasiswa Islam Teknik UNM

Youth Department Staff

Himpunan Mahasiswa Elektro UNM

Head of Organizational Development Department

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

Aug 2016 - Dec 2021

Mar 2021 - Present

Jul 2020 - Present

Contact

Profile

Status

Skill & Expertise

Graphic Design

Web Development

Communication Skill

UI Design

089517179488

🔀 achmadfachrul1999@gmail.com

achmadfachrul

in linkedin.com/in/achmad-fachrul

https://achmadfachrul.github.io

jl. Prumnas antang, Komp.Manggala Permai Blok A/6. Makassar Jun 2019 - Jul 2021

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

Feb 2017 - Feb 2018